    export let trivia = [
        {
            question: 'In the Pokémon series, which type is Sudowoodo, the Imitation Pokémon?',
            correct_answer: 'Rock',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Ground',
                    'Steel',
                    'Fighting'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which Elite Four member from the first generation of Pokémon became the champion in the next generation?',
            correct_answer: 'Lance',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Lorelei',
                    '‎Agatha',
                    'Bruno'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'In the 9th Pokemon movie, who is the Prince of the Sea?',
            correct_answer: 'Manaphy',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Kyogre',
                    'Lugia',
                    'Suicune'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the age of Ash Ketchum in Pokemon when he starts his journey?',
            correct_answer: '10',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    '12',
                    '16',
                    '11'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of these Generation 1 Pokemon did NOT have an evolution in Generation 4?',
            correct_answer: 'Jynx',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Tangela',
                    'Magmar',
                    'Magneton'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What was the first Pokémon invented?',
            correct_answer: 'Rhydon',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Pikachu',
                    'Mew',
                    'Clefairy'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What type is Jirachi',
            correct_answer: 'Steel/Psychic',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Ghost/Psychic',
                    'Psychic',
                    'Fairy'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What type of Pokemon does Misty have?',
            correct_answer: 'Water',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Grass',
                    'Fire',
                    'Bug'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which Pokemon does not have a gender?',
            correct_answer: 'Magnemite',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Heatran',
                    'Latios',
                    'Charizard'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Out of these 3 Pokemon spinoffs, which is the first one to air?',
            correct_answer: 'Pokemon Chronicles',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Pokemon Origins',
                    'Pokemon Generations',
                    'Pokemon Adventures on the Orange Islands'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which one of these Pokemon has Ash NOT owned at one point?',
            correct_answer: 'Vespiquen',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Beedrill',
                    'Staraptor',
                    'Lapras'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'When did the Pokemon anime first air?',
            correct_answer: '1997',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    '1998',
                    '2000',
                    '1996'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What is Ditto special move?',
            correct_answer: 'Transform',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Splash',
                    'Captivate',
                    'Helping Hand'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: "Who stole Misty's bike in the anime",
            correct_answer: 'Ash',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Brock',
                    'May',
                    'Gary'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What was the reason for the banning of episode 35 of the "Pokémon Original Series" Anime?',
            correct_answer: 'Guns',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Swearing',
                    'Nudity',
                    'Gore'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of these Pokémon cannot learn Surf?',
            correct_answer: 'Torterra',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Nidoking',
                    'Seaking',
                    'Palkia'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which water-type Pokémon starter was introduced in the 4th generation of the series?',
            correct_answer: 'Piplup',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Mudkip',
                    'Squirtle',
                    'Totodile'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Who is the leader of Team Instinct in Pokémon Go?',
            correct_answer: 'Spark',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Gary',
                    'Blanche',
                    'Candela'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: "Which Pokémon and it's evolutions were banned from appearing in a main role after the Episode 38 Incident?",
            correct_answer: 'Porygon',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Eevee',
                    'Dratini',
                    'Ghastly'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Who is the God Pokémon?',
            correct_answer: 'Arceus',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Mew',
                    'Mewtwo',
                    'Giratina'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Who is the Lord of the Underworld Pokémon?',
            correct_answer: 'Giratina',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Palkia',
                    'Dialga',
                    'Darkrai'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What is Magikarp iconic move?',
            correct_answer: 'Splash',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Tackle',
                    'Flail',
                    'Bide'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the final evolution of Seedoot?',
            correct_answer: 'Shiftry',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Ludicolo',
                    'Nuzleaf',
                    'Exploud'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Who is the leader of Team Galatic?',
            correct_answer: 'Cyrus',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Giovanni',
                    'N',
                    'Saturn'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What Legendary Pokémon can you find in Cerulean Cave?',
            correct_answer: 'Mewtow',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Mew',
                    'Articuno',
                    'Lugia'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Who is the champion of the Unova League in Black2/White2?',
            correct_answer: 'Iris',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Adler',
                    'N',
                    'Caitlin'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Who is the signature Pokémon of Cynthia?',
            correct_answer: 'Garchomp',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Roserade',
                    'Lucario',
                    'Milotic'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What do you need to evolve Gligar?',
            correct_answer: 'Night + Razor Fang',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Day + Razor Fang',
                    'Hapiness + Razor Fang',
                    'Night + Razor Claw'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Who is the Pokémon that possesses the Battle Bond ability?',
            correct_answer: 'Ash-Greninja',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Greninja',
                    'Pikachu',
                    'Charizard'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of the Pokémon have the Intimidate Ability?',
            correct_answer: 'Stantler',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Miltank',
                    'Snorlax',
                    'Tyranitar'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of the Pokémon do not have the Intimidate Ability?',
            correct_answer: 'Metagross',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Mightyena',
                    'Staraptor',
                    'Arbok'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: "What is Paul's, Ash's Rival iconic Pokémon?",
            correct_answer: 'Electivire',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Drapion',
                    'Infernape',
                    'Torterra'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'How much HP does a Energy Root restore?',
            correct_answer: '200',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    '175',
                    '150',
                    '250'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the effect of a Chesto Berry?',
            correct_answer: 'Recover a Pokémon from sleep',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Recover a Pokémon from poison',
                    'Recover a Pokémon from confusion',
                    'Defrost a Pokémon'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the effect of a Focus Sash?',
            correct_answer: 'When this item is held by a Pokémon, if the Pokémon has full HP but is hit by an attack that would knock it out, this item prevents the holder from fainting and keeps it at 1HP. The Focus Sash disappears after use',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'This item, when attached to a Pokémon, causes it to be immune from Ground-type attacks and entry hazards',
                    'When this item is held, if the holder uses an attack on the opponent which is Super Effective, its power is increased by 20%',
                    'When this item is held by a Pokémon, if the holder moves last, its accuracy is increased by 20%'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the effect of a Carbos?',
            correct_answer: "Increases the Effort Values for the Pokémon's Speed stat up by 10EVs until the Pokémon hits 100EVs in this stat. Increases the Pokémon's Happiness",
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    "Increases the Effort Values for the Pokémon's Special Attack stat up by 10EVs until the Pokémon hits 100EVs in this stat. Increases the Pokémon's Happiness",
                    "Increases the Effort Values for the Pokémon's Attack stat up by 10EVs until the Pokémon hits 100EVs in this stat. Increases the Pokémon's Happiness",
                    "Increases the Effort Values for the Pokémon's Special Defence stat up by 10EVs until the Pokémon hits 100EVs in this stat. Increases the Pokémon's Happiness"
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Dubious Disc is required to evolve which Pokémon?',
            correct_answer: 'Recover a Pokémon from sleep',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Porygon',
                    'Porygon-2',
                    'Dusclops'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Who is the seventh Gym Leader of the Sinnoh Region?',
            correct_answer: 'Candice',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Byron',
                    'Volkner',
                    'Gardenia'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'The nature mechanic was introduced in which generation?',
            correct_answer: 'Generation 3 (Ruby/Saphire/Emerald)',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Generation 2 (Gold/Silver/Crystal)',
                    'Generation 4 (Diamond/Pearl/Platinum)',
                    'Generation 1 (Red/Blue/Yellow)'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of these pokémon does not belongs to the Mineral Egg Group?',
            correct_answer: 'Gastrodon',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Onix',
                    'Bronzor',
                    'Garbodor'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Charizard belongs in which Egg Group?',
            correct_answer: 'Dragon Egg Group',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Flying Egg Group',
                    'Field Egg Group',
                    'Monster Egg Group'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'The Lonely nature lowers which stat?',
            correct_answer: 'Defense',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Special Defense',
                    'Special Attack',
                    'Speed'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'The Sassy nature raises which stat?',
            correct_answer: 'Special Defense',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Special Attack',
                    'Attack',
                    'Defense'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'The Timid nature is known to...',
            correct_answer: 'Raise Speed and lower Attack',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Raise Speed and lower Special Attack',
                    'Raise Attack and lower Speed',
                    'Raise Attack and lower Special Attack'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of these move does not possess a possibility to confuse the enemy?',
            correct_answer: 'Fake Out',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Water Pulse',
                    'Confusion',
                    'Dizzy Punch'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What move possess the HM07?',
            correct_answer: 'Dive',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Surf',
                    'Strength',
                    'Rock Smash'
                ]
        },
        {
            question: 'What move possess the HM06?',
            correct_answer: 'Rock Smash',
            incorrect_answers:
                [
                    'Waterfall',
                    'Cut',
                    'Flash'
                ]
        },
    ]